新月
这些狂暴的欢愉往往也终于狂暴
" These violent delights have violent ends,
最是那辉煌的幻灭 如火亲吻火药
"and in their triumph die, like fire and powder,
随吻即逝
"which, as they kiss, consume."
奶奶?
Gran?
Edward 别 她会看见你的
Edward, don't! She'll see you.
好吧
Okay.
Gran 我给你介绍一下...
Gran, I'd like you to meet...
生日快乐 Bella
Happy birthday, Bella.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
我们不是说好了不送礼物的吗?
I thought we agreed, no presents.
我的这份没有包装 所以不算
Well, the one from me's not wrapped, so it doesn't count.
我很喜欢 谢谢 老爸
That's actually great. Thanks, Dad.
这个是你妈妈送你的 我们协调过的
It goes with this one from your mom. We coordinated.
嗯 她协调的我
Well, she coordinated me.
你可以用来放四年级的照片
It's to put your pictures in from senior year.
四年级了啊
Senior year.
- 你怎么一下子变老太婆了? - 我没有 还没那么老呢
- How'd you get so old so fast? - I didn't. It's not that old.
不知道 那是一根白头发吗?
I don't know. Is that a gray hair?
不可能
No. No way.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
哈哈哈 真好笑
That's really funny.
第三名失踪的远足者被认定死亡
Another missing hiker brings the total to three presumed dead.
护林员正在搜寻伤人的动物...
Rangers are searching for the killer animal...
* Situation's all critical *
Situation's all critical
* You've got to look first before you go *
You've got to look first before you go
是Bella Bella!
It's Bella. Bella!
- 早 - 我...
- Hi. - I'm...
今天是大日子啊 Bella
Today's the big day, Bella.
"罗密欧与朱丽叶"论文截止日期
R and J essay due.
- 哦 是的 - 汝在何处 Bella?
- Oh, yeah. - Wherefore art thou, Bella?
我想给你们拍张照片 我妈想让我收集起来
Let me take a picture of you guys. My mom wants me to put together, like,
弄成个盛满记忆的剪贴簿
a scrapbook full of memories.
- 哦 - 当然 来吧
- Oh. - Cool. Yeah.
我拍吧 我不上相
I take them. I'm not in them.
- 别别 过来 - 今天你得一起照
- No, no, no, come here. - Well, you are today.
如果我鼻子被照的很大的话 你得给我PS一下 好吧?
You'll photoshop this if my nose looks big, right?
别担心 相片里有我呐 就没人看你们了
Don't worry, I'm in the picture. No one will be looking at you guys.
很好
That's good.
好了 Cullen来了
Oh, good. Cullen's here.
回聊
Well, talk to you later.
- 生日快乐 - 别提这个
- Happy birthday. - Don't remind me.
嗯
Mmm.
Bella 你的生日是绝对要庆祝的
Bella, your birth is definitely something to celebrate.
- 是啊 但是别庆祝我变老 - 变老?
- Yeah, but my aging's not. - Your aging?
我觉着18岁就担心这事儿 有点过早了
I think 18 is a little young to start worrying about that.
我比你老一岁了
It's one year older than you.
不是的 我109岁了
No, it isn't. I'm 109.
那么 或许我不该交这么老的男朋友
Well, maybe I shouldn't be dating such an old man.
- 嗯 - 那太恶了 我应该深恶痛绝才是
- Mmm. - It's gross. I should be thoroughly repulsed.
啊哈
Uh-huh.
- 我们得上课去了 - 好吧
- We have to go to class. - Okay.
等一下
Wait a second.
有人找你
Someone wants you.
- Bella! - Jacob!
怎么?
What?
你们先聊
I'll leave you to talk.
你好哇 肌肉男 你知道吗 合成类固醇对你有害
Hello, biceps! You know, anabolic steroids are really bad for you.
我只是长大了而已 Bella
Well, I'm just filling out, Bella.
如果咱常在一起玩的话 你就不会这么惊讶了
You know, it wouldn't seem so drastic if we hung out more.
你转学算了 你可以和白人们一起玩
You should switch schools. You can come hang out with the palefaces.
不必了 我更倾向于寄宿学校的排他性
I'm all right. I prefer the rez school's exclusivity.
专收印第安原住民的学校
这里什么烂人都收
They let any old riffraff into this place.
- 明白了 那你为何大驾光临呢? - 嗯
- I see. Then why are you slumming it? - Mmm-hmm.
我只是过来给爱车买配件
I was just buying a part for the Rabbit.
等弄好了你真该过来试一下
You should really come take a ride when it's done.
跑的快吗?
Is it fast?
嗯
Um.
还好吧
It's decent.
- 我开玩笑呢 - 好吧 不错
- I'm kidding. - Okay. Good.
嘿 生日快乐
Hey, happy birthday.
你老爸跟我老爸说了 所以...
Your dad told my dad, so...
是啊 他不说才怪
Yeah, of course he did.
有一天我看到这个 然后我想起你了
I saw this the other day and thought of you.
除恶梦哒
Catches bad dreams.
我正缺这个呢
That's kind of perfect.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
No problem.
- 见到你很高兴 - 是啊 回头再见
- Good seeing you. - Yeah, I'll see you later.
再见
Bye.
凭啥Jacob Black能送你礼物 而我却不能?
So how come Jacob Black gets to give you a gift and I don't?
因为我没有可以回赠你的东西
Because I have nothing to give back to you.
Bella 你的一呼一吸 就给了我全世界
Bella, you give me everything just by breathing.
看到了没? 谢谢
See? Thank you.
- 我别无他求了 - Bella!
- That's all I want. - Bella!
- 生日快乐! - 嘘!
- Happy birthday! - Shh, shh!
我记得我说过不要礼物的
I thought I said no presents.
我已经预见你打开它了 你猜怎么着
I've already seen you open it, and guess what,
你特喜欢它
you love it.
今晚穿上它来我们家
You're gonna wear it tonight. Our place.
拜托了 好不? 肯定有意思
Come on. Please? It'll be fun.
- 好吧 - 太棒了!
- Okay. All right. - Great!
7点见
Okay, I'll see you at 7:00.
Jasper 又控制我的情绪 太不公平了
Jasper, no fair with the mood control thing.
不好意思 Bella 生日...
Sorry, Bella. Happy...
算了
Never mind.
相信我 你不能相信吸血鬼
You can't trust vampires. Trust me.
噢我的爱! 我的妻子!
O my love! My wife!
死神虽然吸干了你甜蜜的气息
Death, that hath sucked the honey of thy breath
却没有力量摧毁你的美丽
hath had no power yet upon thy beauty.
你没有被征服
Thou art not conquered.
美丽的红旗仍然轻拂着你的嘴唇和面颊
Beauty's ensign yet is crimson in thy lips and in thy cheeks.
死神的白旗还未插到那里
And death's pale flag is not advanced there.
我讨厌庆祝生日
I hate being celebrated.
有人比你惨多了 你看罗密欧
There are worse tragedies. I mean, look at Romeo.
因自己纯犯傻行为 害死了他的真爱
Killed his true love out of sheer stupidity.
是啊
Yeah.
然而有一件事我嫉妒他
Though I do envy him one thing.
朱丽叶太完美了
Juliet is, like, perfect.
如果你喜欢那种超级完美的话
If you like that obviously beautiful sort of thing.
不是指她 我意思是自杀
Not the girl, the suicide.
几乎不可能...
It's nearly impossible for...
对某些人来说
For some people.
人类的话 一点毒药
For humans, a little poison,
心脏上插一刀
a dagger to the heart.
有很多不同的选择
There's so many different options.
你为什么这么说?
Why would you say that?
因为我曾考虑过一次
Because I had to consider it once.
我当时不知道能否及时救你
I didn't know if I'd get to you in time.
我得有个类似的准备
I had to come up with some kind of plan.
什么准备?
What was the plan?
就是我会去意大利去惹Volturi家族
That I'd go to Italy and provoke the Volturi.
- 什么家族? - Volturi
- The what? - The Volturi.
现在 有谁能重复一下 最后几行的抑扬格五音步
Now, who'd like to repeat the last few lines of iambic pentameter
来证明刚才认真听了?
just to show they were paying attention?
Cullen先生?
Mr. Cullen?
好的 Berty先生
Yes, Mr. Berty.
啊 我要在这儿永远安息
"O here will I set up my everlasting rest
从我这厌恶人生的躯体上 挣脱厄运的奴役
"and shake the yoke of inauspicious stars from this world-wearied flesh.
眼睛 最后再看一次
"Eyes, look your last.
手臂 最后拥抱一次吧!
"Arms, take your last embrace!
在你的双唇呼吸之处
"And, lips, O you, the doors of breath,
印下堂堂正正的一吻 与死神签下永世的契约!
"seal with a righteous kiss a dateless bargain to engrossing death!"
大家要注意看屏幕
Eyes on the screen, people.
我就这样在这一吻中死去
ROMEO: Thus with a kiss I die.
Volturi家族渊源悠久 能力强大
The Volturi are a very old, very powerful family.
我猜他们是我们这类中 最接近皇家血统的了
I guess they're the closest thing to royalty my world has.
- 那个是Carlisle吗? - 是的
- Is that Carlisle? - Yeah.
他与他们一起住过几十年
He lived with them for a few decades.
他说他们非常文雅 当然 不尊重人类的生命
Described them as very refined. No respect for human life, of course,
但是至少尊重艺术和科学
but a respect for the arts and the sciences, at least.
以及法律
And the law.
尤其是法律
Above all, the law.
吸血鬼有法律?
Vampires have laws?
不是很多
Not very many.
只有一条须强加执行
And only one that's regularly enforced.
是什么?
What is it?
将我们的存在保密
That we keep the existence of our kind a secret.
绝不暴露人前
We don't make spectacles of ourselves,
也不在大庭广众下杀戮
and we don't kill conspicuously.
当然 除非你想死
Unless, of course, you want to die.
你能不说这事了吗?
You gotta stop talking about that.
我不敢想象有人伤害你的情形
I can't even think about someone hurting you.
Bella 唯一能伤害我的只有你
Bella, the only thing that can hurt me is you.
除此之外我什么也不怕
And I don't have anything else to be afraid of.
你说的不对
That's not true.
Victoria? 以后她会来找我的
Victoria? She'll come for me one day.
她决定了 Alice能预见 咱就能做好准备
Alice will see when she decides, and we'll be ready.
我可以保护你
I could protect you
如果你初拥了我
if you change me.
Bella 你已经在保护我了
Bella, you already do protect me.
你是我"活"下去的
You're my only reason
唯一理由
to stay alive,
可能我这样算"活着"
if that's what I am.
但是我的职责是保护你
But it's my job to protect you.
不受任何人伤害 除了我妹妹
From everyone except my sister.
到点了! 到点了!
It's time! It's time. It's time. It's time!
* Your lips are nettles *
Your lips are nettles
* Your tongue is wine *
Your tongue is wine
* You're left as liquid But your body's pine *
You're left as liquid But your body's pine
很抱歉
Sorry about all this.
- 我们试着拦着Alice来着 - 说的好像你能做到似的
- We tried to rein Alice in. - As if that were even possible.
- 生日快乐 Bella - 谢谢
- Happy birthday, Bella. - Thanks.
我从你包包里找到的 你介意吗?
I found it in your bag. You mind?
泡比你大的妞 帅啊
Dating an older woman. Hot.
- 什么? - 你先来 Rosalie
- What? - You first, Rosalie.
这是一个项链 Alice挑的
It's a necklace. Alice picked it out.
谢谢
Thanks.
恩爱一点看看
Show me the love.
这个是Emmett送的
This one's from Emmett.
已经安在你卡车上了
Already installed it in your truck.
终于有个像样的音响了
Finally a decent sound system
- 那辆破的... - 嘿 别说我卡车的坏话
- for that piece of... - Hey! Don't hate the truck.
看看Esme和Carlisle的礼物
Open Esme and Carlisle's.
只是一些让你开心的小礼物
Just a little something to brighten your day.
是啊 最近你看起来气色不好
Yes, you've been looking kind of pale lately.
噢
Ow.
被纸割到了
Paper cut.
Jaz Jaz 没事的 仅仅是一点
Jaz, Jaz. It's okay. It's just a little
血
blood.
带Jasper出去
Get Jasper out of here.
对不起 我不行
I'm sorry, I can't.
得去我办公室缝一下
I'll have to stitch this up in my office.
去看一下Jasper
Check on Jasper.
我肯定他现在肯定很内疚
I'm sure he's very upset with himself,
估计现在除了你 他谁的话也听不进去
and I doubt he'll listen to anyone but you right now.
Edward
Edward.
- 我一直就没想要开派对 - 这不是你的错
- I never wanted to have a party. - It's not your fault.
Jasper断人血的时间 不像我们这么久
Jasper hasn't been away from human blood as long as the rest of us.
你怎么做到的?
How do you do it?
年复一年的练习
Years and years of practice.
你有没有想过简单的那个方法?
Did you ever think of just doing it the easy way?
没有
No.
我知道我想成为什么样的 我想要帮助人们
I knew who I wanted to be. I wanted to help people.
这样让我感到快乐 即使我无论如何都要被罚
It brings me happiness, even if I am damned regardless.
被罚?
Damned?
你指地狱?
Like hell?
Carlisle 你不会被罚下地狱的
Carlisle, you couldn't be damned.
你不会的 不可能
You couldn't. It's impossible.
谢谢你 Bella
Thank you, Bella.
你对我们一直很客气
You've always been very gracious about us.
就是这个原因? 他就是因此不让我变吸血鬼?
So that's it? That's why he won't change me?
换位思考一下
Imagine the situation in reverse. Hmm.
假如你和Edward想的一样
If you believed as Edward does,
你会夺去他的灵魂吗?
could you take away his soul?
你不能保护我
You can't protect me
不受任何伤害
from everything.
某一天 我们总会两两相隔
At some point, something's gonna separate us.
可能是事故或者疾病
It's gonna be an accident or illness
或者衰老
or old age,
只要我还是人类的话 唯一的解决办法就是初拥了我
as long as I'm human. And the only solution is to change me.
那不是解决办法 这叫悲剧
That's not a solution. That's a tragedy.
等我变成老奶奶时你就不会要我了
You're not gonna want me when I look like a grandmother.
Bella 你一点也不懂我对你的感觉吗?
Bella, do you not understand my feelings for you at all?
Carlisle和我说了
Carlisle told me
你对自己灵魂的感觉
how you feel about your soul.
我不相信
I don't believe that.
所以也别担心我
So don't worry about mine.
你该进屋了
You should go inside.
现在还是我的生日
It's still my birthday.
我能要求一件事吗?
So can I ask one thing?
吻我?
Kiss me?
我爱你
I love you.
* Up with your turret *
Up with your turret
* Aren't we just terrified? *
Aren't we just terrified?
* Shale, screen your worry *
Shale, screen your worry
* From what you won't ever find *
From what you won't ever find
* Don't let it fool you *
Don't let it fool you
* Down *
Down
嘿
Hey.
跟我走走去
Just come take a walk with me.
我们要离开福克斯镇了
We have to leave Forks.
为什么?
Why?
Carlisle本该比他看起来老10岁
Carlisle's supposed to be 10 years older than he looks,
人们开始注意到了
and people are starting to notice.
好吧 我得编个理由和Charlie说
Okay, I've gotta think of something to say to Charlie.
你说"我们"...
When you say "we"...
我指的是我的家人和我
I mean my family and myself.
Edward Jasper的意外什么也不是
Edward, what happened with Jasper, it's nothing.
你说的对 什么也不是
You're right. It was nothing,
除了我一直预料的 什么也不是
nothing but what I always expected
和可能发生的事相比 什么也不是
and nothing compared to what could have happened.
你不属于我的世界 Bella
You just don't belong in my world, Bella.
我属于你
I belong with you.
不 你不属于
No. You don't.
我来了
I'm coming.
Bella
Bella,
我不想你接近
I don't want you to come.
你不想要我?
You don't want me?
不想
No.
那样的话一切都不同了
That changes things a lot.
恕我要求太多
But if it's not too much to ask,
你能答应我一件事吗?
can you just promise me something?
不要鲁莽行事
Don't do anything reckless.
为了Charlie
For Charlie's sake.
同样我也答应你一件事作为回报
And I'll promise something to you in return.
这将是你最后一次见我
This is the last time you'll ever see me.
我不会再回来了
I won't come back,
你可以在没有我的打扰下 继续你的生活
and you can go on with your life without any interference from me.
就好像我从未存在过一样 我保证
It will be like I never existed, I promise.
如果是因为我的灵魂 拿走吧 没有你我也不想要啥灵魂了
If this is about my soul, take it. I don't want it without you.
和你的灵魂无关
It's not about your soul.
你只是不配我
You're just not good for me.
不配你是吧
Not good enough for you.
我很抱歉拖了这么久
I'm just sorry I let this go on for so long.
求求你...
Please...
不要...
Don't...
再见
Goodbye.
Edward
Edward.
Edward!
Edward
Edward.
我要再打给Cullen家试试
I'm gonna try the Cullens' place again.
- Cullens家搬走了 Charlie - 可算滚蛋了
- The Cullens left town, Charlie. - Good riddance.
他们去哪了?
Where'd they go?
我们会找到她的 Charlie
We'll find her, Charlie.
- 谢谢 Harry - Charlie!
- Thanks, Harry. - Charlie!
嘿
Hey.
她没事
She's all right.
我来吧 谢谢你 Sam
I got her. Thank you, Sam.
十月
* There's a possibility *
There's a possibility
十一月
* All that I had *
All that I had
* Was all I'm gonna get *
Was all I'm gonna get
Alice 你消失不见了
Alice, you've disappeared,
像其他一切
like everything else.
现在谁能听我倾诉? 我很迷茫
Now who else can I talk to? I'm lost.
十二月
当你走时
When you left,
他也走了
and he left,
你带走了一切
you took everything with you.
我只能看着他走后留下的空桌
But the absence of him is everywhere I look.
就像有人在我胸口重重打了一拳
It's like a huge hole has been punched through my chest.
Bella
Bella.
但我又有点开心
But in a way I'm glad.
唯有这疼痛提醒我 他是真的
The pain is my only reminder that he was real,
你们都是真的
that you all were.
好了 够了
All right. That's it.
什么?
What?
你回杰克逊维尔 和你妈一起住
You're going to Jacksonville to live with your mother.
我不要离开福克斯
I'm not leaving Forks.
Bells 他不会回来了
Bells, he's not coming back.
我知道
I know.
但这不正常 你的行为
It's just not normal, this behavior.
老实说 都快吓死我和你妈了
Quite frankly, it's scaring the hell out of me and your mother.
宝贝 我也不想你走
Baby, I don't want you to leave.
我不想 但还是走吧 回到杰克逊维尔 交些新朋友
I don't, but just go. Go to Jacksonville. Make some new friends.
我喜欢我的老朋友
I like my old friends.
- 你都不见他们了 - 我有
- Well, you never see them anymore. - I do.
我明天和Jessica去逛街
I'm gonna go shopping tomorrow with Jessica.
- 你讨厌逛街 - 我...
- You hate shopping. - I...
我要过个女生之夜
I need a girls' night out.
好吧 女生之夜
All right. Girls' night.
逛街
Shopping.
我喜欢 去买点东西也好
I like it. Go buy some stuff.
嗨 Jessica 是我Bella
Hi, Jessica, it's Bella.
是的 Bella Swan
Yeah, Bella Swan.
不明白你怎么有耐性看完
I don't know why you want to sit through
那些僵尸吃人的场面 而不是看帅哥和美女亲热
all those zombies eating people and no hot guys kissing anybody.
很恶心不是吗 像... 怎么世上有这么多僵尸电影呀?
It's gross. Like... And why are there that many zombie movies anyway?
感觉像是在学麻疯病?
'Cause if it's supposed to, like, draw a parallel about leprosy,
我表弟有麻疯病 这可一点都不好玩
my cousin had leprosy. It's not funny, you know?
算是暗喻用户至上主义吗?
And, like, is it supposed to be a metaphor for consumerism?
像是在说 不要满足于自我...
Because don't be so pleased with your own, like,
自作聪明啥的
self-referential cleverness, you know?
就像 有些女孩喜欢逛街 但不是所有的女孩都喜欢
Like, some girls like to shop. Not all girls, apparently.
我还是很惊讶你会打电话约我
Although I was surprised you even called at all. You know?
你的失落 我明白 我真的 真的很担心
Like, your depression thing, I get it. I'm totally, totally worried.
但过了一阵子后
But after a while it's like,
- 你还在郁闷... - 要搭便车嘛 美女们?
- you're still bumming... - You want a ride, girls?
...我也有过心理波折 就像Mike决定
...and I'm going through stuff, too. You know? Like Mike deciding
他只想和我做朋友
he just wants to be friends.
看看我们找到了什么?
What's up? Look what we found.
这很难
It's hard, you know?
啥时候开始流行"只做朋友"了...
Like, and since when does "just friends"...
- 伙计们 怎么回事? - 看看我们的发现
- What's up guys? - Look what we found.
喔 喔 喔  嘿 你去哪里?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, where you going?
继续往前走
Keep walking.
这里很危险
This is dangerous.
- 丫头 回神 - 来一下下!
- Dude, come on. - Come here for a sec!
我想我认识他们
I think I know those guys.
我们有啤酒! 还有机车!
We got beer! We got bikes!
他们看着不错 但我们能离开吗?
Well, they seem great. Can we go?
我只想去看点东西
I'm just gonna see something.
嘿 美女们
Hey, girlie!
好了 好了 我们有乘客了
All right, all right. We got a taker.
转身
Turn around.
- 闭嘴! - 你给我闭嘴!
- Shut up! - You shut up!
对不起 我把你当别人了
I'm sorry, I thought you were somebody else.
没事 你想把我当谁都可以 宝贝
No, that's cool. I'll be whoever you want me to be, honey.
上来不?
So, what do you say?
你答应过 不会鲁莽
You promised me, nothing reckless.
你也保证说 会像你从来没存在过一样
You promised it would be as if you never existed.
- 你撒谎 - 你说什么 宝贝?
- You lied. - You say something, babe?
管他呢? 算了吧
You know what? Never mind.
停下! 停下 停下 快停下!
Stop! Stop, stop, stop!
嘿 你发什么神经?
Hey, what the hell's wrong with you?
只是有点好奇
Just curious.
- 我以为我看见什么了 - 你... 噢
- I thought that I saw something. - You... Oh.
事实上 你疯了 或者想自杀
You're insane, actually. Or suicidal.
那个老乡可能是个神经病
That homeboy could've been a psycho.
我差点就要像蹩脚电视里的那样 走进FBI的讯问室了
I was about to end up in an FBI interview room like some lame TV show.
天哪 真刺激
God, that was such a rush.
好啊 你有肾上腺素瘾症啦?
Awesome. So you're an adrenaline junkie now?
行啊 那去蹦极好了
That's cool. You can go bungee jumping.
但不要去坐小混混的摩托车
You don't get on the back of some random loser's motorcycle.
疯子
Crazy.
Alice 我看见他了
Alice, I saw him.
也许我疯了 但没关系
Maybe I'm crazy now. I guess that's okay.
如果只有遇险才能见到他
If a rush of danger is what it takes to see him,
我愿意以身犯险
then that's what I'll find.
Bella!
你去哪里了 疯丫头?
Where the hell have you been, loca?
我给你带了点东西
I brought you something.
- 好吧 - 这玩意儿有点疯狂
- Okay. - It's a little crazy.
喔哦
Wow.
破铜烂铁 你真客气
Scrap metal. You shouldn't have.
我从废品站捡来的
I saved it from the junkyard.
我想修理价会比它的身价更高
I think they'll probably cost more to fix than they're worth,
然后我又想到 如果我有个懂机械的朋友
but then I thought that if I had a mechanic friend
- 愿意帮我 那么... - 啊!
- to help me out then... - Ah!
- 我就是那个懂机械的朋友? - 是的
- Me being the mechanic-type friend? - That's right.
- 你啥时候迷上摩托车了? - 现在开始
- Since when are you into motorcycles? - Since now.
如果你认为我很蠢很冲动 我理解
I get it if you think that this is really stupid and reckless.
是的哈 确实很愚蠢 很冲动
Yeah, I mean, it's completely stupid and reckless.
我们什么时候开工?
When do we start?
呃
Um.
现在吧
Now.
- 求你了? - 好吧
- Please? - All right.
噢 嘿 小心点 这些家伙很重的 所以...
Oh, hey, be careful. Those things are actually really heavy, so...
Jake 你真...健壮
Jake, you're, like, buff.
怎么回事? 你不是才16岁嘛 我不明白
How did that happen? You're, like, 16. I don't get it.
呃... 年龄只是个数字 宝贝 你几岁了呢? 40岁?
Mmm-hmm. Age is just a number, baby. What are you, like, 40 now?
我有时会有这种感觉
It feels like that sometimes.
那首歌很好听 你不喜欢吗?
That song's good. You don't like it?
我有点不再迷音乐了
I don't really like music anymore, kind of.
好吧 不听音乐了
Okay. No more music.
我在想 如果我们每天都坚持动工
So I was thinking, if we're gonna do this every day,
但愿我们每天都能开工
and hopefully we will,
我们是否要 在哪里先做点功课
we have to, like, fit some homework in there somewhere.
我不想让Billy觉得我把你带坏了
I don't want Billy thinking that I'm a bad influence on you.
你? 带坏我? 拜托
You? Influence me? Please.
你...我年纪比你大
Are you... I'm older than you,
所以我就是施影响者 而你则是受影响的人
so that makes me the influencer and you the influencee.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
我的个头和知识库 都比你大
My size and knowledge base actually makes me older than you
因为你整日苍白 又不谙世事
because of your general paleness and lack of know-how.
我好歹说服你 跟我一起修理2辆报废机车
I convinced you to build two-wheeled death machines with me.
这没让你觉得自己幼稚天真吗?
Don't you think that makes you kind of young and naive?
好吧 那咱多大?
Okay. So where do we stand?
- 我35岁了 你估计也就32吧 - 少来
- I'm 35. And you might be, like, 32. - Come on.
- 哟 Jake 在家吗? - 没事 是我哥们
- Yo, Jake, you in there? - It's okay. It's just my boys.
- 嘿 Jake - 嘿 伙计们 这位是Bella
- Hey, Jake. - Hey. Guys, this is Bella.
- Bella 这两位是Quil和Embry - 嗨
- Bella, that's Quil and Embry. - Hi.
我叫Quil Ateara
I'm Quil Ateara.
这么说还真有修机车这事
So the bike building story is true.
噢 是的 没错 我手把手教会他
Oh, yeah, yeah, I taught him everything he knows.
那么你是他女朋友这话可是当真?
What about the part where you're his girlfriend?
呃...
Uh...
我们是朋友
We're friends, you know.
- 糗大了 - 实际上
- Burn. - Actually,
记得我是这么说的 她是女性-朋友
remember I said she's a girl and a friend.
Embry 有记得他这么区分吗?
Embry, do you remember him making that distinction?
没有
Nope.
你们都有女朋友? 很赞哇
So you guys have girlfriends? That's awesome.
嗯 是的 Quil带他表妹去参加毕业舞会
Yeah, right. Quil's actually taking his cousin to prom.
是啊 也算轰动嘛
Yeah, that's still a riot.
想搞笑嘛 Black? 那我让你爽一下
You want funny, Black? I'll give you funny.
见鬼
Jeez.
嘿 这么抱算着犯规!
Hey, that hold's illegal!
我压5块钱赌Quil赢
I got five bucks on Quil.
赌就赌
You're on.
* All of the astronauts Champagne in plastic cups *
All of the astronauts Champagne in plastic cups
* Waiting for the big hero to show *
Waiting for the big hero to show
* Outside the door he stands His head in his hands *
Outside the door he stands His head in his hands
* And his heart in his throat *
And his heart in his throat
*What can he tell them now*
What can he tell them now
亲爱的Alice
Dear Alice,
真希望能有你的真实地址
I wish I had your real address.
真希望能跟你讲讲Jake
I wish I could tell you about Jake.
他让我的好过很多
He makes me feel better.
他让我感觉生机勃勃
I mean, he makes me feel alive.
我胸口的伤痛
The hole in my chest,
和Jake在一起时 好像痊愈了
well, when I'm with Jake, it's like it's almost healed
有那么一阵子
for a while.
Quil一直说要来这里 我想他有点喜欢你过头了
So, Quil keeps asking to come over. I think he likes you a little too much.
噢
Oh.
我对姐弟恋可没兴趣 懂不?
Well, I'm really not into the whole cougar thing. You know?
你和你年纪较啥劲呢?
What's up with you and age?
Cullen那家伙又几岁了?
I mean, how old was that Cullen guy, anyway?
但 即使Jake也没办法赶走梦魇
But even Jake can't keep the dreams away.
嘿 嘿 嘿!
Hey, hey, hey!
醒醒 Bella
Wake up, Bella.
你没事 你没事
You're okay. You're okay.
我还以为这玩意儿有用 看样子没用
I thought this thing was starting to work, but I guess not.
能问你点事吗?
Can I ask you something?
和Jacob一起玩
Hanging out with Jacob,
好像有点转移你的注意力 不是吗?
that seems to take your mind off things a bit, doesn't it?
有时候
You know, sometimes
你得学会去爱对自己有益的事物
you gotta learn to love what's good for you.
懂我的意思吗?
You know what I mean?
当然 我知道个啥呢?
Of course, what do I know?
我只不过是个终极单身汉
I'm just a terminal bachelor.
出了名得有女人缘
Famous ladies' man.
好了
Okay.
我去睡觉了
I'm gonna go to bed.
呃...
Uh...
我爱你
I love you.
如果我说 我没法修好摩托车 你会说什么?
If I told you I couldn't have fixed these bikes, what would you have said?
你在怀疑自己的疯狂技能?
Are you doubting your mad skills?
不 当然不是 它们能跑起来
No. Definitely not. I mean, they'll run fine.
只是
It's just,
如果我够聪明 我应该放慢维修速度
maybe if I was smart, I would have dragged out the rebuild a bit.
如果你说你不能修好摩托车 我会说 真糟糕
If you told me you couldn't fix these bikes, I would say that that's really too bad,
那我们只能去找别的事做了
but that we're just gonna have to find something else to do.
那个是Sam Uley吗?
Is that Sam Uley?
是的 他和他的信徒
Yeah. Him and his cult.
噢 天哪
Oh, my God.
你看到了吗?
Did you see that?
他们不是真打架 Bella 他们在玩悬崖跳水
They're not really fighting, Bella. They're cliff diving.
非常恐怖 但是很刺激
Scary as hell, but a total rush.
- 刺激? - 大部分人都选择矮的地方跳
- A rush? - Most of us jump from lower down.
就让Sam和他的门徒显摆好了
We leave the showing off to Sam and his disciples.
你跟他有啥过节?
You have some kind of beef with him or something?
我不知道
I don't know.
他们觉得自己拥有这个地方
They just think they run this place.
Embry以前称他们为 打了类固醇的纠察队员
Embry used to call them hall monitors on steroids.
- 瞧他现在这样子 - 那个是Embry?
- Now look at him. - That's Embry?
- 是的 - 他怎么回事?
- Yeah. - What happened to him?
他翘了几天课
He missed some school.
突然之间 他开始做Sam的跟屁虫
Now all of a sudden, he started following Sam around like a little puppy.
Paul和Jared也这样
Same thing happened with Paul and Jared.
Sam不停地用怪异的眼神看我
Sam keeps giving me this look,
好像他在等我或什么的
like he's waiting for me or something.
我觉得有点恐怖
It's kind of starting to freak me out.
你还是躲着他比较好
Well, you should just avoid him.
我在努力
I try.
好了
Okay.
- 你好像很怕 - 我不怕
- You look scared. - I'm not.
好吧
All right.
- 刹车? - 那个
- Brake? - That one.
离合器?
Clutch?
很好
Good.
汽油?
Gas?
准备好了吗?
Ready?
慢慢松开离合器
Now, slowly release the clutch.
Bella
Bella.
停下
Stop.
你没事吧?
You all right?
我再试一次
I'm gonna go again.
好的
Okay.
踩刹车!
Hit the brake!
我要再来一次
I wanna go again.
你想自杀吗?
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
- 不 我要再试一次 - 不 想都别想
- No. I want to go again. - No. Forget it.
不准再骑机车
No more bikes.
噢 你的额头
Man, your head.
- 是的 - 噢 天哪 对不起
- Yeah. - Oh, my God, I'm sorry.
什么 你为自己流血而道歉?
What, you're apologizing for bleeding?
我想是的
Yeah. I guess I am.
只流了一点血 Bella 不严重
Well, it's just blood, Bella. No big deal.
来
There.
你盯啥呢?
What are you staring at?
你长得还挺帅
You're sort of beautiful.
你脑子被撞傻了?
How hard did you hit your head?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我确实在树林里看见过
I did see something in the woods.
宝贝 我相信你
Totally. Baby, I believe you.
不 他不信 他只想撞运罢了
No, he doesn't. He's just trying to get lucky.
没有 那玩意乌黑乌黑的 非常大
No, okay. It was jet black and huge.
四脚触地 还比人要高
On all fours, it was still taller than a person.
可能是熊?
A bear, maybe?
或者是外星人 你没被针戳算你走运
Or an alien. You're lucky you didn't get probed.
我看见它了
Well, I saw it.
不只你看见过
You know, you're not the only one.
我爸爸在警局接到举报
My dad's been getting reports at the station.
5个背包客被啥熊杀害
Like, five hikers have been killed by some bear.
但却一直找不到那只熊
But they can't find the bear.
呃
Hmm.
这是你们丫最后一次敢怀疑我女朋友
Last time you clowns doubt my girlfriend.
呃...
Um...
那么...
So? I mean,
Bella回来了?
Bella's back?
我想是的
Yeah, I guess so.
很好 这个...  欢迎你
All right, that's... Well, welcome.
听着 既然你又开始说话
So, listen, now that you're talking
吃饭 你好歹得补点蛋白质
and eating again, which, you know, you've got to get that protein in there,
不知...你要不要和我一起去看电影
I was just wondering if you wanted to go see a movie with me.
嗯 当然了 是的 我愿意
Yeah. Sure. Yeah, I do.
很好
Cool.
我们可以去看
Let me see, we could check out
"终究是爱"
Love Spelled Backwards Is Love.
片名有点俗 但是部浪漫喜剧
You know, it's a dumb title, but it's a romantic comedy.
- 应该会蛮... - 不 不要浪漫的
- I mean, it's supposed to be pretty... - No. No romance.
"一击即中"怎么样? 听说过这部电影吗?
How about Face Punch? Have you heard of that?
是部动作片
I mean, that's an action movie.
嗯 很完美
Yeah, that's perfect.
枪械 肾上腺素
Guns, adrenaline.
是我的茶
That's my thing.
好吧
Okay.
我们应该多叫几个人一起 你们想去看"一击即中"吗?
We should get a bunch of people to go. Do you guys want to go see Face Punch?
"一击即中" 耶!
Face Punch, yeah!
Mike 嘿 我们说要去看的
Mike, hey, we were supposed to watch that.
还记得嘛 那个预告片...
Remember, the trailer's like...
- 超火爆的 - 我记得
- "Punch faces." - I remember.
耶! 和Bella共度电影之夜
Yeah! Movie night with Bella.
"一击即中"哈?
So Face Punch, huh?
你喜欢动作片?
You like action movies?
不是很喜欢
Not really.
听说不好看 很烂
I heard it sucks. Bad.
你够年纪看这电影?
Are you even old enough to see this movie?
没有成人监督下可以吗?
I mean, you know, without, like, adult supervision.
噢 她在帮我买票
Right, yeah, well, she's buying my ticket for me.
她在买 好的
She's buying it. Okay.
Jessica耍约 Angela得了肠胃炎
Jessica bailed, and Angela got the stomach flu,
Eric在照顾她
so Eric's taking care of her.
- 只有我们仨 - 很好!
- It's just us three. - Great!
- 很好 - 是的
- Great. - Yeah.
把枪放下
Put your gun down.
你把枪放下 否则我就打爆你的脑袋
Put your gun down or I'm gonna blow your frickin' head off.
你们俩都把枪放下
Both of you put both of your guns down
否则我就打爆你们俩的脑袋
or I'm gonna blow both of your frickin' heads off.
好吧 算了 我们开战吧!
All right, forget it, let's do this!
我想我要吐了
Okay, I think I'm gonna throw up.
他...
He's...
真是脆弱啊!
What a marshmallow!
你得找个肠胃坚强点的人
You should hold out for someone with a stronger stomach.
嘲笑让懦弱男人呕吐的血腥场面的人
Someone who laughs at the gore that makes weaker men vomit.
好的 我会留意的
Yeah. I'll keep my eye open for that.
我好内疚哦 他可能得了流感了
I feel bad. He probably has that flu that's going around.
怎么了 我不能牵你的手吗?
What? I can't hold your hand?
能 你当然能
No, of course you can.
我只是认为这动作对你来说有特殊含义 所以...
I just think it means, you know, something a little different to you. So...
好吧 说出来吧 你喜欢我 对吧?
Okay, well, tell me something. You like me, right?
而且你觉得我挺帅的?
And you think I'm sort of beautiful?
Jacob 拜托 不要这样
Jacob, please, don't do this.
为什么?
Why?
因为你会毁了这一切的
Because you're about to ruin everything.
而且我需要你
And I need you.
我有大把的时间
Well, I've got loads of time.
我不会放弃的
I'm not gonna give up.
我也不想你放弃
I don't want you to,
但那只因我不想你离开
but it's just 'cause I don't want you to go anywhere.
这真是自私啊
And that's really selfish.
我不像一辆能被你修好的汽车
You know, I'm not like a car that you can fix up.
我再也不会正常行驶了 所以我对你该公平些
I'm never gonna run right. So I should be fair to you.
都是因为他 是不是?
It's because of him, right?
听着
Look,
我知道他对你做了什么
I know what he did to you.
但是Bella 我永远也不会那样做的
But, Bella, I would never ever do that.
我永远也不会伤害你 我发誓
I won't ever hurt you. I promise.
我不会令你失望的
I won't let you down.
你能依靠我
You can count on me.
好了
Well,
我得回家了
I need to go home.
电影前我就觉得想吐了
I was feeling sick before the movie. Okay?
你啥毛病呐?
What is your problem?
现在吗? 就是你
Right now? You're my problem.
想吐? 或许你应该去医院了
Feeling sick? Maybe you need to go to the hospital.
想让我把你送进医院吗
You want me to put you in the hospital?
Jake 电影都放完了 你这是在干什么?
Jake! Jake. Jake, the movie's over. What are you doing?
你身上真热
You're really hot.
好像发烧了似的 你还好吗
Like, you feel like you have a fever. Are you okay?
我不知道怎么了
I don't know what's happening.
我得走了
I gotta go.
那家伙太奇怪了
That dude is weird.
Jake 你爸说你得了单细胞核增多症
Jake, your dad says you have mono.
他不让我来看你 你能回个电话吗
He won't let me visit, but would you call me?
嘿 还是我 我只是...
Hey, it's me again. I just...
对于在电影院说过的话我很抱歉
I'm sorry about what I said at the movie theater.
我只是想听听你的声音 别紧张
I just wanted to hear your voice, so no pressure.
Jacob 拜托
Jacob, please...
给我打电话
Call me.
我们大概三点回来
Okay. We should be back around 3:00.
嘿
Hey.
我今天不是非去钓鱼不可
Look, I don't have to go fishing today.
你得去
Yes, you do.
是的 你要去 走吧 还在说什么
Yeah, you do. Go. What are you talking about?
注意安全
Just be careful.
向来如此
Always am.
那些熊打不过我的 Bella
Those bears won't get the drop on me, Bella.
我功夫很厉害的
My kung fu is strong.
Jake
Jake!
嘿
Hey!
你剪了头发?
You cut your hair off?
做了纹身?
And got a tattoo?
Bella
Bella.
我以为你病的出不了门呢
I thought you were too sick to come outside
或者接不动我电话呐
or pick up the phone when I call.
走开
Go away.
什么?
What?
走开
Go away.
你怎么了 什么事儿
What happened to you? What's...
嘿 发生什么了
Hey! What happened?
Sam找你了 就是这事儿吗?
Did Sam get to you? Is that what's happening?
Sam想帮我 不要怪他
Sam's trying to help me. Don't blame him.
如果你想怪谁
But if you want somebody to blame,
你深爱的那些个肮脏的吸血鬼怎么样 Cullen一家?
how about those filthy bloodsuckers you love, the Cullens?
我不懂你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
不 你知道的清清楚楚
No, you know exactly what I'm talking about.
你向每个人都撒了谎 Charlie
You've been lying to everyone. Charlie.
但是你不能欺骗我
But you can't lie to me.
- 再也不能了 Bella - Jacob!
- Not anymore, Bella. - Jacob!
Jacob!
听着 Bella
Look, Bella,
我们不能再做朋友了
we can't be friends anymore.
Jake 我知道我伤害了你
Look, Jake, I know that I've been hurting you.
我备受折磨 像死一样难过
It's killing me. It kills me.
我只是需要...给我点
I just need... Maybe give me, like,
- 时间或什么的 - 不用了
- some time or something. - Look, don't.
不是因为你
It's not you.
不怪你 是我 对吗?
It's not you, it's me, right? Really?
是真的 因为我
It's true. It is me.
我不够好
I'm not good.
我曾经是个乖孩子的
I used to be a good kid.
再也不是了
Not anymore.
这一点儿也不重要 行吗
This doesn't even matter. All right?
全结束了
This is over.
你不能和我分手
You can't break up with me.
我是说...
I mean...
你是我最好的朋友啊
I mean, you're my best friend.
你保证过的
You promised me.
我知道
I know.
我保证过不会伤害你 Bella
I promised I wouldn't hurt you, Bella.
我正在坚守我的誓言
And this is me keeping that promise.
回家吧
Go home
不要回来 不然你会受伤的
and don't come back or you're gonna get hurt.
Alice
Alice,
一切都...
things are...
又变的糟糕了
Things are bad again.
没有了Jake 我...我坚持不下去了
Without Jake, I just... I can't stand it.
我再没见到Edward了
I don't see Edward anymore.
真能做到像他从未存在过一般么?
Will it really feel like he never existed?
我会找到能见到他的地方
I will find the place where I can see him again.
Bella
Bella.
Laurent
Laurent.
没想到在这儿能见到你
I didn't expect to find you here.
我去拜访Cullen一家 但房子空了
I went to visit the Cullens, but the house is empty.
我真惊讶他们把你留下了
I'm surprised they left you behind.
你不就如
Weren't you sort of
他们的个宠物吗?
a pet of theirs?
是 可以这么说吧
Yeah. You could say that.
Cullen一家经常看你吗?
Do the Cullens visit often?
撒谎
Lie.
是的 当然 一直有来
Yeah, absolutely, all the time.
编好点
Lie better.
我会告诉他们你来过的
I'll tell them that you stopped by.
或许我不应该
But I probably shouldn't
告诉Edward
tell Edward,
因为他太保护我了
'cause he's pretty protective.
但是他远在天边 不是吗
But he's far away, isn't he?
你为什么来这?
Why are you here?
算是帮Victoria一个忙
I came as a favor to Victoria.
- Victoria? - 她让我来看看
- Victoria? - She asked me to see
你是不是还在Cullen庇护之下
if you were still under the protection of the Cullens.
鉴于Edward杀了她的伴侣
Victoria feels it's only fair to kill Edward's mate,
Victoria觉得只有杀了他的才够公平
given he killed hers.
以牙还牙
An eye for an eye.
威胁他
Threaten him.
Edward会知道是谁干的 他会找你算账的
Edward would know who did it. And he'd come after you.
我不这么认为
I don't think he will.
毕竟 他把你毫无庇护地丢在这儿
After all, how much could you mean to him
你对他能算是什么?
if he left you here unprotected?
我杀了你Victoria会不高兴的
Victoria won't be happy about my killing you,
但我忍不住
but I can't help myself.
你太令人垂涎欲滴了
You are so mouth-watering.
- 求你不要 你帮过我们的 - 不不不
- Please, don't. I mean, you helped us. - No, no, no, no.
别害怕 我这是在帮你
Don't be afraid. I'm doing you a kindness.
Victoria打算慢慢折磨死你
Victoria plans on killing you slowly,
痛苦地
painfully,
但是我会很快了结你
whereas I'll make it quick.
我保证
I promise.
你什么都感觉不到
You will feel nothing.
Edward 我爱你
Edward, I love you.
我不相信
I don't believe it.
- 爸 我看见它们了 - 怎么了?
- Dad! I saw them. - What's the matter?
- 在树林里 不是熊 - 在树林里 什么意思?
- In the woods. They're not bears. - What do you mean "in the woods"?
Bell 你去树林里干什么
Bell, what the hell were you doing out in the woods?
它们是狼 巨型的狼
They're wolves. I mean, they're like huge wolves.
你确信 Bella?
Are you sure about that, Bella?
是的 我刚刚看见它们 它们在追赶着什么
Yeah! I just saw them. They were after something.
狼?
Wolves?
你看见它们了?
You saw them?
好吧 Harry
All right, well, Harry,
想打猎么 把你的伙计们聚起来?
feel like going hunting? Get some of your guys together?
当然 只是...
Sure, yeah, I'll just...
眼下那些狼该没命了
By now, those wolves will be dead,
Laurent会告诉她我毫无保护
and Laurent would have told her I'm unprotected.
Victoria
Victoria.
我要去局里
I should go to the station.
是的 你应该去
Yeah, you should. You should go.
你能待在屋里吗?
Can you just stay in the house?
Bella
Bella!
你吓着我了
You scared me.
- 你到底在干什么? - 后退 我要上来了
- What the hell are you doing? - Back up. I'm coming up.
嘿
Hey.
听着 我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
- 为什么? - 真希望我能解释
- For what? - I wish I could explain.
但我真不能说
But I literally can't.
你有过不能告诉任何人的秘密吗?
Have you ever had a secret you couldn't tell anyone,
不能与他人分享的秘密?
one that wasn't yours to share?
我就是这样
Well, that's what it's like for me.
但更糟糕
But worse.
你不知道我被拘束得多紧
You have no idea how tight I'm bound.
我讨厌这样
I hate this.
我恨他们对你做的
I hate what they've done to you.
我是说 吸血鬼的那部分 你已经知道了
I mean, the killer part is, you already know.
Bella 你记得我们在拉普什海滩上散步吗?
Bella, do you remember when we walked on the beach at La Push?
那个...
The...
那个关于
The story. The story about
吸血鬼的故事
the cold ones.
我已经知道为什么你只记得那部分了
I guess I understand why that's the only part you remember.
一定有些什么你能做的
There's gotta be something that you can do.
不 我生来如此
No. I'm in it for life.
或许我们应该离开一阵子
Well, maybe we should just get out of here for a while.
只管离开
Just leave,
只有你和我
just you and me.
你愿意这样?
You'd do that?
为了你 我会的
I would do it for you.
这不是我能一逃了之的事情 Bella
It's not something I can just run away from, Bella.
但如果可以
But I would run away with you
我会和你一起逃开
if I could.
我要走了 他们会起疑我去哪儿了
I gotta go. They'll start wondering where I am.
过来
Come here.
请你
Please,
试着记住
try to remember.
如果你知道一切
It'd be so much easier
你会好受很多
if you knew.
我会的 但是Jake...
I'll try. But, Jake...
Jake 你在干什么 等等 Jake
Jake, what are you doing? Wait, Jake.
Jake
Jake.
Edward 我很害怕
Edward, I'm scared.
你应当如此
You should be.
这只是个古老传说了
Really, it's just like an old story.
我真的应该什么也不说的
I'm not really supposed to say anything about it.
你知道Quileute族是狼的后代吗?
Did you know Quileutes are supposedly descended from wolves?
Bella
Bella?
我要见他
I need to see him.
他不在
He's not in.
- 我很抱歉 我真的需要见见他 - Bella
- Okay, I'm sorry, I really need to see him. - Bella!
你们做什么了
What did you do?
- 你们都做了什么? - 嘿
- Okay, what did you do? - Hey.
- 你们对他怎么样了? - 放松
- What did you do to him? - Easy!
他不想这样
He didn't want this.
我们做什么了 他呢 他告诉你什么了?
What did we do? What did he do? What'd he tell you?
- 你们都冷静点儿 - 什么也没有
- Both of you calm down. - Nothing.
他什么也没告诉我 因为他害怕你们
He tells me nothing because he's scared of you.
- 太迟了 - Bella 回去
- Too late now. - Bella, get back!
Paul 冷静下来 现在
Paul, calm down, now!
Bella
Bella!
快跑
Run!
Jake 快跑
Jake, run!
Paul
Paul!
嘿 把Bella带回Emily那儿
Hey! Take Bella back to Emily's place.
看起来狼的秘密暴露了
Guess the wolf's out of the bag.
Alice 这一切有可能是真的吗?
Alice, is it possible that everything is true?
童话和恐怖故事
The fairy tales and horror stories?
是否可能理智与正常根本不存在?
Is it possible that there isn't anything sane or normal at all?
嘿 我觉得该回去看看Jacob是不是安好了
Hey, I think we should go back and see if Jacob's okay.
我希望Paul用牙咬他 他是罪有应得
I hope Paul sinks some teeth in him. Serves him right.
没可能 Jacob是天才
No way. Jacob's a natural.
你看他跑时的样子没? 我打包票Paul根本碰不到他
You see him phase on the fly? I got five says Paul doesn't touch him.
进来 Bella 我们不会咬你的
Come on in, Bella. We won't bite.
说你自己呢吧
Speak for yourself.
* I done me wrong *
I done me wrong
* And done all wrong *
And done all wrong
* All the wrong I've done I'm sure I'll live quite long *
All the wrong I've done I'm sure I'll live quite long
嘿 Emily Sam的未婚妻 别盯着看 Sam最讨厌那样
Oh, hey, about Emily, Sam's fiance? Don't stare. It bugs Sam.
我为什么要盯着
Why would I stare?
伙计们饿了没 真是明知故问
Are you guys hungry? Like I have to ask.
这位是
Who's this?
Bella Swan 还能有谁
Bella Swan. Who else?
嗯
Hmm.
那么 你是吸血鬼的女友
So, you're the vampire girl.
那么 你是狼人的女友
So, you're the wolf girl.
算是
Guess so.
我都和个狼人订婚了
Well, I'm engaged to one.
给你兄弟留点儿吧 女士优先 要松饼吗?
Save some for your brothers. And ladies first. Muffin?
当然 谢谢
Sure. Thanks.
让Jacob自己想办法琢磨Sam的禁言令吧
Leave it to Jacob to find a way around Sam's gag order.
他什么也没对我说
He didn't say anything to me.
那是狼族的事儿
That's a wolf thing.
老大的命令要无条件服从
Alpha's orders get obeyed whether we want them to or not.
知道吗 我们能读懂彼此的想法
And check it out. We can hear each other's thoughts.
能闭嘴么 这些可是秘密 丫的!
Would you shut up? These are trade secrets. Damn it!
这小妞和吸血鬼一路的
This chick runs with vampires.
我可跟不上他们的脚步
You can't really run with vampires.
他们太快了
'Cause they're fast.
真的么 我们速度更快
Yeah? Well, we're faster.
吓到了没?
Freaked out yet?
你不是我见到的第一个怪物了
You're not the first monsters I've met.
Jake说对了 你很能接受奇怪事物
Jake's right. You're good with weird.
嘿
Hey.
抱歉
Sorry.
那么 你是狼人?
So you're a werewolf?
是的 千真万确
Yeah. Last time I checked.
部落里一小部分幸运儿有这个基因
A few lucky members of the tribe have the gene.
吸血鬼搬进城了 我就全身发烧
A bloodsucker moves into town and the fever sets in.
单核细胞增多症
Mono.
我倒希望是
Yeah. I wish.
你们找不到方法停止吗?
Well, can't you find a way to just stop?
我的意思是 这不对
I mean, it's wrong.
这可不是选择生活方式 Bella
It's not a lifestyle choice, Bella.
天生的 我也管不住
I was born this way. I can't help it.
你真虚伪 怎么 我不是你要的那款怪物?
You're such a hypocrite. What, I'm not the right kind of monster for you?
这无关你是什么种族
It's not what you are.
是你做了什么 他们从未伤害任何人
It's what you do. They never hurt anybody.
你们杀人了 Jake
You've killed people, Jake.
Bella 我们没杀过任何人
Bella, we're not killing anyone.
那是谁干的?
Then who is?
我们试图保护你们人类免受他们伤害的
What we're trying to protect you people from,
那些我们唯一杀的
the only thing we do kill,
吸血鬼
vampires.
等下 Jake 你不能
Wait, Jake, you can't.
别担心 我们不会动你的宝贝Cullen一家
Don't worry. We can't touch your little precious Cullens
除非他们违反契约
unless they violate the treaty.
我不是这个意思
That's not what I'm saying.
你们不能杀吸血鬼 他们会...
You can't kill vampires. They'II...
他们会杀了你的
They'll kill you.
真的吗 我们把那个吸血鬼轻易了结了
Really? We took out that leech with the dreads easy enough.
Laurent?
他的红发女友是下一位
And his red-headed girlfriend is next.
Victoria在这儿?
Victoria's here?
曾经在 那晚我们一路追踪她到加拿大边境
Was. We chased her all the way to the Canadian border the other night.
她总回来 我们不知道她要找什么
She keeps coming back. We don't know what she's after.
我知道
I do.
我
Me.
别担心 我们严守这一块儿
Don't worry. We've got this place covered.
她不会接近你和Charlie的
She won't get near you or Charlie.
你小心点
Look, you've got to be careful.
她速度很快 远远超越你的想象
She's fast. You don't know how fast she is.
你对我们没信心 有点侮辱人哦
You know, your lack of confidence in us is a little insulting.
好吧 我得走了
All right, I'd better go.
你要走吗?
You gotta go?
是
Yeah.
去猎杀吸血鬼
Got a vampire to kill.
Alice 我没事
Alice, I'm all right.
除了有些孤单
Until I'm alone.
最近始终如此
And lately, that's all the time.
Jacob走了 他去猎杀Victoria
Jacob's gone. He's hunting Victoria.
而Charlie在猎杀Jacob
And Charlie's hunting Jacob.
你又走了
And you're gone.
Edward也走了
And so is Edward.
于是现在空无一片
And there's just nothing now.
你有发现吗 Harry?
You got something, Harry?
没 没有
Nope. Nothing.
但我知道我该去哪里
But I realize where I have to go,
我必须做什么才能再次见他
what I have to do to see him again.
* A tear in my brain *
A tear in my brain
* Allows the voices in *
Allows the voices in
* They wanna push you off the path *
They wanna push you off the path
* With their frequency wires *
With their frequency wires
* And you can do no wrong *
And you can do no wrong
* In my eyes *
In my eyes
* You can do no wrong *
You can do no wrong
* In my eyes *
In my eyes
* A drunken salesman *
A drunken salesman
* Your hearing damage *
Your hearing damage
* Your mind is restless *
Your mind is restless
* They say you're getting better *
They say you're getting better
* But you don't feel any better *
But you don't feel any better
* Your speakers are blowing *
Your speakers are blowing
* Your ears are wrecking *
Your ears are wrecking
* Your hearing damage *
Your hearing damage
* You wish you felt better *
You wish you felt better
* You can do no wrong *
You can do no wrong
* In my eyes *
In my eyes
别这么做
Don't do this.
你想让我做人类
You wanted me to be human.
看着我
Watch me.
求你
Please.
为了我
For me.
除此办法之外 你我不能厮守
You won't stay with me any other way.
Bella 求你
Bella, please.
* This constant noise all the time *
This constant noise all the time
* Even though you're the only one I see *
Even though you're the only one I see
呼吸!
Breathe!
醒醒!
求你了 Bella 醒醒!
Come on, Bella, breathe!
Bella Bella 能听到我吗?
Bella? Bella, can you hear me?
Jake?
过来
Come here.
你想什么呢你?
What the hell were you thinking?
我只是想看一些东西
I just wanted to see something.
送她回家! 我去帮Harry的忙
Get her home! I'm gonna go help out over at Harry's place.
Harry怎么了?
What happened at Harry's?
据说Harry心脏病发作
Harry Clearwater had a heart attack.
Charlie和我爸去慰问他的家人了
Charlie and my dad are over at his place with his family.
他还好吗?
Is he okay?
他过世了
He's gone.
来 我帮你弄干然后送你回家
Come on. I'll get you something dry and drive you home.
我身上热的很呐
108 degrees over here.
老天!
God!
我的手冻僵了
My hands are freezing.
永不会冷的感觉一定很棒
It must be nice, never getting cold.
狼人都会如此
It's a wolf thing.
不
It's not.
只有Jacob这样
It's a Jacob thing.
你真的很温暖
You're just warm.
你就像太阳一样
You're like your own sun.
这样更好 现在你了解我了
This is better, now that you know about me.
但...
But...
你看到Emily的事了吧
You saw what happened to Emily.
Sam怒了
Sam got angry.
只是一秒钟的失控
Lost it for a split second.
而Em当时站得太近
Em was standing too close.
他永远无法挽回了
He'll never be able to take that back.
如果我对你怒了该如何?
What if I got mad at you?
有时
Sometimes,
我感觉自己快要消失
I feel like I'm gonna disappear.
并不是说 你需要我
Okay, not that you need me
对你说这样的话
to tell you something like this,
但我会一直提醒你 你不会迷失自己
but I always will. You're not gonna lose yourself.
我不会让那种事发生的
I wouldn't let that happen.
怎么做?
How?
我会一直对你说
I'll tell you all the time
你是多么与众不同
how special you are.
谢谢 为我所做的一切
Thank you. For everything.
等等
Wait.
这里有个吸血鬼
There's a vampire.
你怎么知道?
How do you know?
我可以闻到 我带你离开这
I can smell it. I'm getting you out of here.
那是Carlisle的车
That's Carlisle's car.
他们在这里
They're here.
Bella 是个圈套 停! 你跟我走!
Bella, it's a trick! Stop! You gotta come with me!
他们不会伤害我的
They won't hurt me.
如果Cullen一家回来  这里是他们的领地
If a Cullen is back here, this is their territory.
契约规定我们只保卫自己的领地
Treaty says we can only defend on our own lands.
- 在这里我不能保护你 - 好的 没事 不必
- I can't protect you here. - Okay. That's okay. You don't have to.
你好像打算越界
You're about to cross a line.
那就别划界线
Then don't draw one.
求你?
Please?
Alice?
- 哦 老天! 你怎么... - Bella!
- Oh, my God! What are you... - Bella!
抱歉 我只是 我只是无法相信你会在这儿 你...
I'm sorry, I just, I can't believe you're here. Is...
能给我解释一下你怎么活下来的吗?
Would you like to explain to me how you're alive?
什么?
What?
我在幻象中看到你跳崖
I saw a vision of you. You jumped off a cliff.
你究竟为何要自杀?
Why in the hell would you try and kill yourself?
Charlie怎么办?
I mean, what about Charlie?
- 怎么办... - 我不是尝试自杀
- What about... - I didn't try to kill myself.
我是要跳崖
I was cliff jumping.
闹着玩的!
Recreationally.
有趣而已
It was fun.
我从没见过如此不顾性命的蠢行
I have never met anyone more prone to life-threatening idiocy.
你...
Does...
你告诉他了吗?
Did you tell him?
没
No.
他只是每几个月来一个电话
He only calls in once every few months.
他说他想独处
He said he wants to be alone.
Bella 为什么闻起来 会有可怖的落汤狗的味道?
Bella, what is that God-awful wet dog smell?
嗯...
Um...
可能是我
That's probably me.
或者Jacob的气味
Or it's Jacob.
Jacob是谁?
Jacob who?
Jacob是狼人
Jacob's kind of a werewolf.
Bella!  狼人可不是什么志趣相投的伙伴
Bella! Werewolves are not good company to keep.
说你自己呢吧
Speak for yourself.
我来看看你是否安全
I had to see you were safe.
我记得你说在这你不能保护我
I thought you couldn't protect me here.
也许我不在意这些了
Guess I don't care.
我不会伤害她的
Well, I'm not gonna hurt her.
是 你是一个无害的Cullen家的人
No, you're just a harmless Cullen.
我说的是另外一个吸血鬼 因为你们而想杀了Bella
I'm talking about the other bloodsucker who tried to kill Bella because of you.
Victoria?
是的 Victoria曾在附近出现
Yeah, Victoria's been around.
我没看见过她
I didn't see her.
我也没看见有人把你从水里救出
I didn't see you get pulled out of the water, either.
我看不见你和你们那群疯狗
I can't see past you and your pack of mutts.
别惹我...
Don't get me upset...
- 嘿 停 停 停 停 - ...否则给你难堪
- Hey, stop. Stop, stop, stop, stop. ...or things are gonna get very ugly.
我给你们点时间
I'll give you a minute.
嗨
Hey.
别去其他地方 到时回这来
You're not going anywhere. You're gonna come back,
- 对吗? - 你一赶走这只狗我就回来
- right? - As soon as you put the dog out.
他...
Is he...
还有其他Cullen家的人在吗?
Are there others? How many Cullens are here
他们要待多久?
and how long are they staying?
没
No.
只有Alice一个
It's just Alice.
她随便待多久都可
And she can stay as long as she'd like.
那其他人会回来吗?
Well, are the rest coming back?
不
No.
据我所知不会
Not that I know of.
还有别的事吗?
Anything else?
就这些
That's it.
如果没事 那你最好赶快回Sam那里
Well, if that's all, then you'd better go run back to Sam.
我又这么做了
I've done it again.
不断违背我的誓言
I keep breaking my promise.
我们之间不必如此
We don't have to do this to each other.
不 需要
Yes, we do.
Bella...
这里是Swan家
Swan residence.
他现在不在
He's not here right now.
他安排葬礼去了
He's arranging a funeral.
哪位?
Who was that?
怎么了?
What?
总是挡道
Always in the way.
是谁?
Who was that?
Bella 退后
Bella, step back.
- Jake 是谁? - Bella! Bella 是Edward
- Jake, who was that? - Bella! Bella, it's Edward.
他以为你死了 Rosalie告诉了他我来这的原因
He thinks you're dead. Rosalie told him why I came here.
你为什么...不让我跟他说话?
Why would you... Why didn't you let me speak to him?
- 他没有找你 - Bella
- He didn't ask for you. - Bella.
- 我不在乎! - Bella Bella 他要去找Volturi家族
- I don't care! - Bella. Bella! He's going to the Volturi.
他也想死
He wants to die, too.
他抛弃了你 Bella 他不再要你 记得吗?
JACOB: He left you, Bella. He didn't want you anymore. Remember?
不 我不能让他因为内疚而去送死
No, I'm not gonna let him kill himself out of guilt.
那你爸爸怎么办?
What about your dad?
我18岁了 从法律上讲我行动自由 而我也留了纸条
I'm 18. I'm legally free to go, and I left a note.
求你 Bella
Please, Bella,
留下
just stay here.
为Charlie
For Charlie.
或为我
Or for me.
我必须去
I have to go.
我求你
I'm begging you.
求你
Please.
再见 Jacob
Goodbye, Jacob.
好吧
Okay.
你打定主意了哈
So you've made up your minds.
我有点可惜你的天赋
I'm afraid your particular gifts
如此珍贵不应毁灭
are too valuable to destroy.
如果你惋叹命运不幸 可加入我们
But if you're unhappy with your lot, join us.
我们也乐意利用你的的能力
We would be delighted to utilize your skills.
你何不考虑下留在我们这里吗?
Won't you consider staying with us?
你明知早晚会如此
You know it will happen anyway.
但不会毫无由头
Not without cause.
暴殄天物!
Such a waste.
我猜这辆你不是租来的吧?
I'm guessing you didn't rent this car?
我想你眼下不会介意我偷车
I figured you wouldn't be opposed to grand theft auto.
今天不会
Not today.
怎么了? 你看到什么了?
What? What do you see?
他们拒绝了他
They refused him.
- 那? - 他想暴露身份
- So? - He's gonna make a scene.
- 把自己的身份暴露给人类 - 不! 什么时候?
- Show himself to the humans. - No! When?
他会等到正午 太阳升到最高点
He's gonna wait until noon, when the sun's at its highest.
天呢 Alice 你开快点
God, Alice, you got to hurry up.
那就是沃特拉
There's Volterra.
- 为何他们都身着红装? - 庆祝圣马库斯节
- Why are they all in red? - San Marco's Day festival.
纪念吸血鬼被逐出这个城市
They're commemorating the expulsion of vampires from the city.
背景很完美
It's the perfect setting.
在此暴露 Volturi家族绝不会放过他
The Volturi will never let him get far enough to reveal himself.
我们只有5分钟
We have five minutes.
我知道 Bella 深呼吸
I know, Bella, just breathe.
Alice!
Bella 你是唯一一个他不会想到会来的人
Bella, you're the only one he can't see coming.
换成我 他会读我思维 他会因为我的欺骗而选择速死
If I go, he'll read my thoughts. He'll think I'm lying. He'll rush into it.
- 我去哪找? - 他就在钟塔下面 快!
- Where do I go? - He'll be under the clock tower. Go!
别!
Don't!
这是天堂
Heaven.
必须进去
You have to move.
睁开眼睛 看看我 我还活着
Open your eyes. Look at me. I'm alive.
必须进去
You have to move.
Bella
Bella.
- 你来了 - 是我
- You're here. - I'm here.
你还活着
You're alive.
对
Yes.
我想让你再次看到我
I needed to make you see me once.
必须让你知道我还活着
You had to know that I was alive,
这样你就不必内疚
that you didn't have to feel guilty about anything.
现在我可以让你走了
I can let you go now.
我绝不是因为内疚
I never acted out of guilt.
没有你我活不下去
I just couldn't live in a world where you don't exist.
- 但你说... - 我骗你的
- But you said... - I lied.
我必须撒谎 但你却那么轻易就信了
I had to lie. But you believed me so easily.
因为你爱我 这说不通啊
Because it doesn't make sense for you to love me.
我一无是处 我是人类 无关紧要
I mean, I'm nothing. I'm human. I'm nothing.
Bella 你于我是一切
Bella, you're everything to me.
全部
You're everything.
我现在不需要你们的帮忙了 绅士们
I won't be needing your services after all, gentlemen.
Aro想再次跟你聊聊
Aro wants to speak with you again.
没有破坏规矩
No rules were broken.
虽说如此 咱应该到个更适合的审判地谈吧
Nonetheless, we should take this conversation to a more appropriate venue.
好吧
Fine.
Bella 要不你和大家一起欢度节日?
Bella, why don't you go and enjoy the rest of the festival?
这女孩必须跟我们一起走
The girl comes with us.
不 你去死吧
No. You can go to hell.
别逗了 伙计们
Come on, guys.
这是庆祝节日 你们也不愿引起骚动
It's a festival. You wouldn't want to make a scene.
我们不想
We wouldn't.
够了
Enough.
Jane
Jane.
Aro派我来看下为何要这么久
Aro sent me to see what was taking so long.
按她吩咐的意思做
Just do as she says.
你们先请
Go ahead.
别害怕
Don't be scared.
你呢?
Are you?
不
No.
- 她是人类? - 是
- Is she human? - Yes.
她知道这一切?
Does she know?
是
Yes.
那为何...
Then, why would...
想要成为...
She wants to be.
她会转变的
And so she will be.
或者成为甜点
Or dessert.
妹妹 让你抓一个你却带回来两个
Sister. They send you out to get one and you bring back two.
还有半个
And a half.
真是个聪明姑娘
Such a clever girl.
真是个惊喜!
What a happy surprise!
Bella终究还是活着呐
Bella is alive after all.
简直棒极了哈?
Isn't that wonderful?
我喜欢圆满的结局
I love a happy ending.
啊
Ah.
罕见啊
They are so rare.
她甜美的鲜血如此吸引你
Her blood appeals to you so much
都让我饥渴了
it makes me thirsty.
你距她一步之遥何以忍住?
How can you stand to be so close to her?
- 并不容易 - 是 我可以理解
- It's not without difficulty. - Yes, I can see that.
Aro只要轻轻一摸 就可以知道我所有的想法
Aro can read every thought I've ever had with one touch.
现在你知晓一切了
And now you know everything.
那就继续吧
So get on with it.
你的读心术也很不错啊 Edward
You are quite a soul reader yourself, Edward.
尽管如此你却无法获悉Bella的想法
Though you can't read Bella's thoughts.
妙啊!
Fascinating.
我很愿意看看你是否也能防御我的能力
I would love to see if you are an exception to my gifts, as well.
肯赏光吗?
Would you do me the honor?
有趣
Interesting.
嗯
Hmm.
我什么都没有读到
I see nothing.
我非常好奇...
I wonder if...
让咱看看她是否对我们所有的能力都免疫
Let us see if she's immune to all our powers.
能展示下吗 Jane?
Shall we, Jane?
- 不! - 疼痛
- No! - Pain.
住手!
Stop!
住手! 求你! 住手!
Stop! Please! Stop!
住手! 别伤害她! 求你! 求你!
Stop! Just stop hurting him! Please! Please!
Jane?
主人?
Master?
继续 亲爱的
Go ahead, my dear.
这可能会有些痛
This may hurt just a little.
太不可思议!
Remarkable!
她挫败了我们所有人
She confounds us all.
那我们现在该如何处置你呢?
So what do we do with you now?
你已知道怎么做 Aro
You already know what you're going to do, Aro.
她知道的太多了
She knows too much.
她是个负担
She's a liability.
嗯
Hmm.
的确如此
That's true.
Felix?
不!
No!
求你! 不! 不! 求你! 求你!
Please! No! No! Please, please!
杀了我! 杀了我! 别伤害他
Kill me! Kill me! Not him.
多特别啊!
How extraordinary.
你竟然愿意为我们这类放弃生命
You would give up your life for someone like us.
为吸血鬼
A vampire.
一群无魂的怪物
A soulless monster.
放她走!
Just get away from her!
你对他的灵魂一无所知
You don't know a thing about his soul.
真是悲剧!
This is a sadness.
只要你有意使她永生
If only it were your intention to give her immortality.
等等!
Wait!
Bella会成为我们的一员
Bella will be one of us.
我预见到了
I've seen it.
我来初拥她
I'll change her myself.
令人着迷!
Mesmerizing.
能遇见尚未发生之事
To see what you have seen before it has happened.
你的天赋将成就一个有趣
Your gifts will make for an intriguing
而不朽的
immortal,
Isabella
Isabella.
去吧
Go now.
做好准备
Make your preparations.
我们来亲自来处理
Let us be done with this.
Heidi随时会到
Heidi will arrive any moment.
感谢你们的拜访
Thank you for your visit.
我们也会热情回馈
We will return the favor.
我建议你们立即实现诺言
I would advise that you follow through on your promise soon.
下不为例
We do not offer second chances.
再见 我的年轻朋友们
Goodbye, my young friends.
收获不错 Heidi
Nice fishing, Heidi.
是 他们的确看来诱人
Yes, they do look rather juicy.
给我留点
Save some for me.
走这边 一起走
This way, please. Stay together.
停! 停!
Stop! Stop!
你还在
You're here.
安心睡吧
You can sleep.
你睡醒前我都会守着你
I'll still be here when you wake up.
Bella 我离开你的唯一原因
Bella, the only reason I left
是我以为我是在保护你
was because I thought I was protecting you.
我希望你
I needed you
有机会过上正常快乐的生活
to have a chance at a normal, happy life.
你可以那么轻易的离开我
It was so easy for you to leave.
离开你是我这一百年最艰难的事
Leaving you was the hardest thing I've done in 100 years.
我发誓
And I swear,
我不会再辜负你
I will never fail you again.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
- Charlie来了 - 嗨
- Charlie's coming. - Hey.
你还好吗?
You okay?
还好
I'm fine.
爸 你不必担心我
Dad, you don't have to worry.
上次你这样说 你出走了
You know, last time you said that, you took off.
三天都不见
I didn't see you for three days.
我真的很抱歉 爸爸
I'm really sorry, Dad.
Bella 别再这么对我
Bella, do not ever do that to me again.
永远别
Ever.
你被禁足了哦
And you're grounded
终生禁足哦
for the rest of your life.
好吧
Okay.
严格说 我没有违反他的规定
I'm not technically breaking any of his rules.
他的确有说 我不能踏进门内一步
He did say I couldn't take a step inside the door.
我是从窗子进来
I came in through the window.
他不会这么容易原谅我的
He's not gonna forgive me easily.
我知道
I know.
你呢?
Can you?
我希望你能
I hope you can,
因为没有你 我真的不知如何生活
'cause I honestly don't know how to live without you.
过来
Come here.
一旦Alice把我转变
Once Alice changes me,
你就别想再抛弃我
you can't get rid of me.
她不一定要转变你
She won't need to change you.
一定还有别的方法可以瞒住Volturi家族
There are always ways to keep the Volturi in the dark.
不 不
No. No.
你们都知道我想要的
You all know what I want.
而我也知道我的要求有些过分
And I know how much I'm asking for.
我认为唯一公平的是大家投票表决
The only thing that I can think of for it to be fair is to just vote.
- 你不知道你在说什么 - 闭嘴
- You don't know what you're talking about. - Shut up.
Alice?
我已经把你当成我的姐妹了
I already consider you my sister.
- 我同意 - 谢谢
- Yes. - Thank you.
我也投"同意"
JASPER: I vote "yes."
这样我就不用一直想要杀你
It would be nice to not want to kill you all the time.
嗯
Hmm.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我为之前的行为向你两道歉
I'm really sorry to both of you for how I've acted,
而且我真感激的是你足够勇敢
and I'm really grateful that you were brave enough
去救我弟弟
to go and save my brother.
但换了我 我不会选择这样的生活
But this isn't a life I would have chosen for myself.
如果是我 我希望有人能阻止我
And I wish that there'd been someone to vote "no" for me.
故此 我反对
So, no.
我当然投"同意"
I vote "Hell, yeah."
我们用别的方法打击Volturi家族
And we can pick a fight with these Volturi some other way.
我早把你当成是家庭的一员了
I already consider you a part of the family.
我同意
Yes.
你为什么要这样对我?
Why are you doing this to me?
你知道里边的含义
You know what this means.
你选择没她不活 这让我别无选择
You've chosen not to live without her, which leaves me no choice.
我不想失去我的儿子
I won't lose my son.
我想等到毕业以后再做 这样子Charlie会好过些
I'll wait until after graduation to make it easier on Charlie.
Edward 我希望由你亲自来做
Edward, I want you to be the one to do it.
他想和我聊会
He wants to talk to me.
因此你现在还活着
So you're still alive for now.
他认为是我把你带远了
He thinks it's me keeping you away.
别读我的想法
You stay the hell out of my head.
Jacob 我知道你有话对我说
Jacob, I know you have something to say to me.
如果可以的话 我想先对你说点什么
But I want to say something to you first, if that's all right.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你在我不在的时候保护Bella
Thank you for keeping Bella alive when I didn't.
不 你确实不在
No. You didn't.
我不是为你保护她 相信我
And it wasn't for your benefit, trust me.
我还是很感激
I'm still grateful.
但现在我回来了
But I'm here now.
除非她赶我走否则我不会离开她
I'm not gonna leave her side until she orders me away.
咱们走着瞧
We'll see.
该我说了
Hey, my turn to talk.
我提醒你别忘记我们契约的一个重点
I'm here to remind you about a key point in the treaty.
我没忘
I haven't forgotten.
什么重点?
What key point?
如果你们中任何人咬了人类
If any of them bites a human,
停战就会结束
the truce is over.
但如果我是自愿 就不关你事
But if I choose it, it has nothing to do with you.
不 不 我不会让你
No. No, I won't let you.
你不能变成他们的一份子 Bella
You're not gonna be one of them, Bella.
这你不能决定
It's not up to you.
你知道我们会怎样对你 我别无选择
You know what we'll do to you. I won't have a choice.
Bella 拜托 走吧
Bella, please, come.
等等
Wait.
他会伤害我吗? 读他的想法
Is he gonna hurt me? Read his mind.
Jake
Jake,
我爱你
I love you.
所以 求你
So, please,
不要逼我抉择
don't make me choose,
因为我一定选他
'cause it'll be him.
一直就是他
It's always been him.
Bella...
- 再见 Jacob - 不 不用你为她说
- Goodbye, Jacob. - No, you don't speak for her!
Bella 咱们走
Bella, get out of here.
停!
Stop!
你们互相伤害 我也不能幸免
You can't hurt each other without hurting me.
Jake
Jake.
他是对的
He's right.
你不该变成我这样
You shouldn't become what I am.
我一个人做不到
I can't do this alone.
那就请等等
Then, please, just wait.
给我五年的时间
Just give me five years.
这太长了
That's too long.
那么三年?
Then three?
你真固执
You're so stubborn.
你要等什么?
What are you waiting for?
我有一个条件
I have one condition
如果你要我亲自来的话
if you want me to do it myself.
什么条件?
What's the condition?
约束永远
And then forever.
正如我愿
That's what I'm asking.
嫁给我 Bella
Marry me, Bella.
新月 -=结束=-
White demon love song down the hall
White demon shadow on the road
Back up your mind, there is a call
He isn't coming after all
Love this time
She likes the way he sings
White demon love song's in her dreams
White demon, where's your selfish kiss?
White demon sorrow will arrange
Let's not forget about the fear
Black invitation to this place that cannot change
While strangely holy
Come for a rain
White demon, widen your heart's scope
White demon, who let your friend go?
- Let us be in love - Let us be in love
- Let's do old and gray - Let's do old and gray
- I won't make you cry - I won't make you cry
- I will never stray - I will never stray
- I will do my part - I will do my part
Let us be in love tonight
White demon, widen your heart's scope
White demon, who let your friend go?
Stand it anymore, darling
Stand it
Meet me on the equinox
Meet me halfway
When the sun is perched at its highest peak
In the middle of the day
Let me give my love to you
Let me take your hand
As we walk in the dimming light
Oh, darling, understand
That everything, everything ends
Meet me on your best behavior
Meet me at your worst
For there will be no stone unturned
Or bubble left to burst
Let me lay beside you, darling
Let me be your man
And let our bodies intertwine
But always understand
That everything, everything ends
That everything, everything, everything ends
A window
An opened tomb
The sun crawls
Across your bedroom
A halo
A waiting room
Your last breaths
Moving through you
As everything, everything ends
As everything, everything, everything
Everything, everything, everything ends
Meet me on the equinox
Meet me halfway
When the sun is perched at its highest peak
In the middle of the day
Let me give my love to you
Let me take your hand
And as we walk in the dimming light
Oh, darling, understand
That everything, everything ends